Proper, Carl UNITE Publications 6000/057 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Carl Proper UNITE Publications
1968-2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Proper, Carl
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Workers (UNITE)
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
UNITE-HERE
6000/057 PUBS
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
8686981
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 07, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 07, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
roper, Carl; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Workers (UNITE); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU); UNITE-HERE
8686981
- 20 Years of Caring, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 20 Years of Caring, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- America at Work, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: America at Work, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: AFL-CIO Public Affairs Deparment
    Notes: v.7:no.5 (2002:June)
- Behind Closed Doors: The Workers Who Make Our Clothes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Behind Closed Doors: The Workers Who Make Our Clothes, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: National Labor Committee
    Notes: University Students Investigate Factories in Central America
- Constitution of the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: UNITE
- Cooperrative Partnership: A New Beginning for National Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of America, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cooperrative Partnership: A New Beginning for National Steel Corporation and the United Steelworkers of America, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Bureau of Labor-Management Relations
    Notes: BLMR 114
- Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1, 1983 to December 31, 1985 Financial report to the 39th convention, May 30, 1986.
  - Item 2: Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1, 1983 to December 31, 1985 Financial report to the 39th convention, May 30, 1986. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Employer Contributed Benefit Funds, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: January 1, 1983 to December 31, 1985 Financial report to the 39th convention, May 30, 1986. Copy 3.
- Fashion Forward, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Fashion Forward, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: Council for American Fashion (CAF)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1990:Jan.)
  - Item 2: Fashion Forward, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1990:Jan.) Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Fashion Forward, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1990:Sept.)
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: January 1, 1980 to December 31, 1982 Financial report to the 38th convention, May 27, 1983.
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 1, 1986 to December 31, 1988 Financial report to the 40th convention, June 2, 1989.
- Financial and Statistical Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Financial and Statistical Report, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: January 1, 1992 to December 31, 1994 Financial report to the 42th convention, June 23, 1995.
- Financial Report: General Funds, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Financial Report: General Funds, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Auditing Department
  - Item 2: Financial Report: General Funds, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Financial Report: General Funds, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Financial Report: General Funds, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Financial Report: General Funds, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Financial Report: General Funds, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Financial Report: General Funds, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Flexible Manufacturing Systems, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Flexible Manufacturing Systems, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Ed Hill
    Notes: March 18, 1992. Clemson Apparel Research, Clemson University
- The Garment Center: Still in Fashion, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Garment Center: Still in Fashion, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: New York Industrial Retention Network
    Notes: A Land Use Analysis of the Special Garment Center District, April 2001. Special Report to the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) and Council for American Fashion (CAF)
- High Fashion, High Tech, High Skill (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: High Fashion, High Tech, High Skill (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Notes on the Future of the American Apparel Industry. Empty conference folder.
  - Item 2: High Fashion, High Tech, High Skill (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Notes on the Future of the American Apparel Industry. Empty conference folder. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: High Fashion, High Tech, High Skill (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: Notes on the Future of the American Apparel Industry. Empty conference folder. Copy 3.
- A Human Resource Development Strategy for the New York City Garment Industry, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A Human Resource Development Strategy for the New York City Garment Industry, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Garment Industy Development Corporation (GIDC)
    Notes: October, 1987. Prepared for the New York City Office of Business Development
- Keeping Jobs in Fashion, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Keeping Jobs in Fashion, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Richard Rothstein
    Notes: Alternatives to the Euthanasia of the U.S. Apparel Industry
- Keeping New York in Fashion, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Keeping New York in Fashion, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Author: Kurt Salmon Associates
    Notes: A Strategic Plan for The Future of the New York Fashion Apparel Industry. March, 1992.
- Labor Management Committees: A Process for All Seasons, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Labor Management Committees: A Process for All Seasons, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Author: Greater Wilkes-Barre Area Labor Management Council
- Made in China: Behind the Label, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Made in China: Behind the Label, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Author: Charles Kernagham
    Notes: March, 1998.
- Made in New York: The Future of Manufacturing in the City of New York, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Made in New York: The Future of Manufacturing in the City of New York, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Author: Mitchell L. Moss
    Notes: August, 1994.
- Methods of Price Settlement Under Joint Dress Board (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Methods of Price Settlement Under Joint Dress Board (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Author: Bernice Taylor
- New York City Apparel and Textiles Industry Analysis, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: New York City Apparel and Textiles Industry Analysis, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Author: Matthew T. Mitchell
    Notes: Draft: April 9, 1999
- An Outline of Grievance Procedures in the Garment Industry, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: An Outline of Grievance Procedures in the Garment Industry, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Author: William J. Mathews; Oliva Reusing
    Notes: A Membership Trainging Manual Published by the Northeast Department
- Path to Prosperity, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Path to Prosperity: Securing the Future of Southern California's Apparel Industry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Author: Southern California Apparel Roundtable
    Notes: Review Draft, April 1994.
- The Pattern of Garments (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Pattern of Garments (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Author: Gus Tyler
- Paying to Lose Our Jobs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Paying to Lose Our Jobs, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Prospects for Long-Term Occupancy of Factory Space by the Lower Manhattan Garment Industry, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Prospects for Long-Term Occupancy of Factory Space by the Lower Manhattan Garment Industry, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Resolutions: 39th Convention, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Resolutions: 39th Convention, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Notes: May 30, 1986.
- Restyling the Los Angeles Apparel Industry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Restyling the Los Angeles Apparel Industry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Author: Jean Gilberrt
    Notes: Models, Options, and Resources for Industry Revitalization, June 1994.
- SEW What?, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: SEW What?, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Author: Bruse G. Herman
    Notes: The New York apparel industry in the global economy: Inevitable decline or possibilities fo industrial upgrade?
- "Sweatshops" in New York City, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: "Sweatshops" in New York City: A Local Example of a Nationwide Problem, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Author: U.S. General Accounting Office
    Notes: June 1989. Briefing Report to the Honorable Charles E. Schumer, House of Representatives.
- "Sweatshops" in the U.S., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: "Sweatshops" in the U.S.: Opinions on Their Extent and Possible Enforcement Options, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Notes: August 1988. Briefing Report to the Honorable Charles E. Schumer, House of Representatives.
- Technology Changes in the Garment Industry, Vol. 10, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Technology Changes in the Garment Industry, Vol. 10, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Author: Mitchell Lokiec
- The U.S. in Haiti: How To Get Rich on 11 an Hour, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The U.S. in Haiti: How To Get Rich on 11 an Hour, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- UNITE!, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2001:Winter)
  - Item 2: UNITE!, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (2002:Invierno)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 3: UNITE!, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (2003:Spring)
  - Item 4: UNITE!, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (2003:Fall)
- UNITE Auto Parts Plants: Industrial Audit Survey, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: UNITE Auto Parts Plants: Industrial Audit Survey, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Author: UNITE Research Department
    Notes: December 1996.
- UNITE for the Future, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: UNITE for the Future, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Notes: June 1999. Report of Proceedings of the First Constitutional Convention
- UNITE for the Future, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: UNITE for the Future, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Notes: June 1999. Report of Proceedings of the First Constitutional Convention. Copy 2.
- UNITEHERE!, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: UNITEHERE!, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Author: UNITE HERE
    Notes: Annual Report Fall 2006
    Language: Spanish; English.
- UNITEHERE! Constitution, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: UNITEHERE! Constitution, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- UNITEHERE! Local Unions and Affiliates, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: UNITEHERE! Local Unions and Affiliates, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Notes: April 2011.
- Welcome to UNITE! (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Welcome to UNITE! Fighting for our future (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: Welcome to UNITE! Fighting for our future (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Notes: Copy 2.
- Was Your School Cap Made in this Sweatshop (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Was Your School Cap Made in this Sweatshop (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Item 2: Was Your School Cap Made in this Sweatshop (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Women's Wear Daily, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Women's Wear Daily, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Author: Women's Wear Daily (WWD)
    Notes: Monday, January 29, 2001. Partial
  - Item 2: Women's Wear Daily, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: Monday, May 13, 2002. Partial
  - Item 3: Women's Wear Daily, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: Tuesday, May 21, 2002. Complete
  - Item 4: Women's Wear Daily, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: Wednesday, May 22, 2002. Partial
  - Item 5: Women's Wear Daily, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: Tuesday, May 28, 2002. Partial
  - Item 6: Women's Wear Daily, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Notes: Thursday, June 6, 2002. Complete